export const chapter = "Chapter - 10: Popular Beliefs and Religious Debates";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Which three deities were specifically worshipped during the ancient period?",
        optionA: "Brahma, Vishnu, Shakti",
        optionB: "Shiva, Vishnu, Durga",
        optionC: "Ganesha, Lakshmi, Saraswati",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What concept became popular in South India towards the middle of the eighth century during the medieval period?",
        optionA: "Karma",
        optionB: "Dharma",
        optionC: "Bhakti",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who were the saints devoted to Lord Shiva during the Bhakti movement in South India?",
        optionA: "Alvars",
        optionB: "Nayanars",
        optionC: "Sufis",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which philosophy did Shankaracharya advocate during the medieval period?",
        optionA: "Dvaita",
        optionB: "Vishishtadvaita",
        optionC: "Advaita",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Ramanuja, a South Indian saint, propagated which philosophy?",
        optionA: "Advaita",
        optionB: "Vishishtadvaita",
        optionC: "Dvaita",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Basavanna, born in Karnataka, opposed what aspect of temple worship?",
        optionA: "Rituals and ceremonies",
        optionB: "Meditation and chanting",
        optionC: "Pilgrimages and fasting",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who wrote the famous Ramcharitmanas and popularized devotion to Lord Rama?",
        optionA: "Mirabai",
        optionB: "Tulsidas",
        optionC: "Surdas",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Sikh Guru established the Khalsa Panth?",
        optionA: "Guru Nanak",
        optionB: "Guru Gobind Singh",
        optionC: "Guru Tegh Bahadur",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which Sufi order did Muinud-din Chishti, Baba Farid, and Nizam-ud-din Auliya belong to?",
        optionA: "Chishti Silsilah",
        optionB: "Suhrawardi Silsilah",
        optionC: "Qadiri Silsilah",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which Sufi saints have their durgahs in Multan, Gujarat, and Sylhet?",
        optionA: "Muinud-din Chishti, Baba Farid, Nizam-ud-din Auliya",
        optionB:
          "Sheikh Baha-ud-din Zakariya, Shah Alam Bukhari, Sheikh Shihab-ud-din Suhrawardi",
        optionC: "Nasir-uid-din Chirag-i-Dilli, Saiyid Muhammad Gesudaraz",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The three deities specifically worshipped during the ancient period were Shiva, Vishnu, and ___________.",
        optionA: "Lakshmi",
        optionB: "Durga",
        optionC: "Brahma",
        correctAnswer: "Durga",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The concept of Bhakti became popular in South India towards the middle of the eighth century. The Nayanars and the Alvars started the Bhakti movement, and the Nayanars were devoted to Lord Shiva, while the Alvars were devoted to Lord ___________.",
        optionA: "Brahma",
        optionB: "Vishnu",
        optionC: "Ganesha",
        correctAnswer: "Vishnu",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Shankaracharya, an eighth-century saint, established four peeths in the corners of India: Badrinath, Puri, Dwarika, and ___________.",
        optionA: "Varanasi",
        optionB: "Rameshwaram",
        optionC: "Ayodhya",
        correctAnswer: "Rameshwaram",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Ramanuja, a South Indian saint born in the eleventh century, preached that devotion to God and compassion for fellow beings can help attain God. He laid down the philosophy of Vishishtadvaita, where he emphasized the unity of the individual soul with the Ultimate God while maintaining its individual ___________.",
        optionA: "Existence",
        optionB: "Identity",
        optionC: "Knowledge",
        correctAnswer: "Identity",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Basavanna, born in Karnataka, opposed all types of discrimination on the grounds of caste or gender. He taught that all human beings are equal and that God resides in the temple called ___________.",
        optionA: "Stone",
        optionB: "Heart",
        optionC: "Body",
        correctAnswer: "Body",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Mirabai, a Rajput princess, abandoned all luxuries for the sake of her devotion to Lord Krishna. She faced many hardships but had unflinching faith in ___________.",
        optionA: "Rituals",
        optionB: "Bhakti",
        optionC: "Sufism",
        correctAnswer: "Bhakti",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Guru Nanak, born at Talwandi, preached true love for God. He established a center at Kartarpur and composed hymns. His teachings included nam-japna (chanting God's name), kirt-karna (honest work), and ___________.",
        optionA: "Langar (community kitchen)",
        optionB: "Fasting",
        optionC: "Pilgrimages",
        correctAnswer: "Langar (community kitchen)",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Kabir Das, born in Kashi in the fifteenth-sixteenth century, emphasized that all people are equal, irrespective of religion or caste. He taught his followers to be practical in life and virtues such as honesty, truthfulness, sweet speech, and right ___________.",
        optionA: "Worship",
        optionB: "Action",
        optionC: "Thought",
        correctAnswer: "Action",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Sufi saints settled in different towns and won followers from both Hindus and Muslims. Their teachings, much like those of the Bhakti saints, professed love for both God and fellow beings. They were called pirs or gurus and practiced various ways to please God, including singing, dancing, and ___________.",
        optionA: "Meditation",
        optionB: "Pilgrimages",
        optionC: "Quawwalis",
        correctAnswer: "Quawwalis",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Chishti Silsilah included important Sufi saints like Muinud-din Chishti, Baba Farid, and Nizam-ud-din Auliya, whose durgahs are located in Ajmer, Hansi, and ___________ respectively.",
        optionA: "Delhi",
        optionB: "Jaipur",
        optionC: "Agra",
        correctAnswer: "Delhi",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "After independence, India's urban spaces no longer show colonial influence.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Urbanization occurs when a town comes into being and prominence due to various causes.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "De-urbanization only occurs due to political reasons.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Surat regained its importance primarily due to the trade in silk.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Hill Stations were established during the colonial period as a response to extreme cold climates in India.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Local self-government in municipalities was introduced by Lord Ripon.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Municipalities in towns are primarily funded by the central government.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Public Works Department (PWD) is responsible for the operation of various facilities like schools and parks.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The first railway line was laid down in India in 1902.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The police organization in colonial India was known for its popularity and integrity among the common people.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
